[Music]
save boost
hey look up there a battery and it's red
like my [__] bald or my [__] ass
when I spank him hahaha Come to Papa
[__] watch out for the knuckles grab
the [__] battery so we can leave what
do you think I've been trying to do for
the past five minutes does he have to
moan every time he jumps is he gay
Knuckles get back in that room right
[__] now we do not leave Collectibles
behind
if you want to see this 10 year old boy
bounds his ass like he's putting on a
show then you can come back and do it
yourself
screw all of you I only rented the game
cause the ass on that toy was insane
let's go downstairs and get a snack
Daddy can you make my friends to make
sandwiches
hell no what makes you think I would
want to cook for all of your stupid
friends but Daddy
shut up [__] I don't want any butts
unless it's yours in my [__] face
Daddy can you please not yell at me in
front of my friends
plus change your pants we can't smell
you
what you can smell him no no you can't
she's right all of us could smell him
ever since we walked in through the
front door
oh my God I had no idea I'm so
embarrassed
I'm not what you're smelling right now
is the grease of a well-oiled machine
a hard-working man and also [__] since I
crapped Myself by accident
but I'm not going to change because this
is my house and I can do whatever the
[__] I want on my property
if you can't handle the steam coming off
of these garlic buns then leave you know
what maybe I'm being too hard on you
kids Mama come over here and rub your
nose in my butt
if you do I will heat you and your
friends up some [__] bagel bites [__]
that [__] you ugly [__] ass
well there it is typical of the younger
generation constantly asking for things
but to unwilling to put in the work
I'm so embarrassed I'm not
we don't need him anyway we can always
run down a quick trip
but manic you know I don't eat fast food
only bad lettuce I didn't mean for you
[__] Daddy needs a taquito
so babe have you ever had the slushie
before
no
then today is going to be your lucky day
why what gave you the idea I wanted one
beach you just asked if I had one before
and I said no on what world would you
have to be for you to have a name thing
but I want one well I was only giving
off a rhetorical question
well done
[Music]
let's go let's go
hey Mindy do you want to see a really
cool life hack I found on Tick Tock okay
first you fill your cup up with Sprite
and the natural flavoring
see now I have a cherry limeade
damn Sonia it's a good thing I don't
have a peanut allergy because your ass
on us
that wasn't even a life hack you dumbass
what makes you say that Knuckles is
Right sis Cherry flavoring offered as an
option completely disproves your
reasonings behind it being a hack
because they expected you to do it
it would be like if I walked into a
public bathroom and life streamed at
bragging that I was using the big boy
potty
what about mixing two drinks together
if they didn't expect you to mix drinks
they would only sell bottles and cans
yacht like in the freezer over there
people who use tiktok are simply low IQ
individuals that fail to see the point
of soda fountains
men do they are eating me alive you have
to back me up on this
pretty colors
bartlebby what are you doing you have to
turn those off right now
nonsense watch this fat boy
[Music]
[Applause]
[__] why did you shut them all off I
was having so much fun you can't just
keep them running like that no matter
how pretty they are people will have to
clean it all up you know
and if they run out there won't be any
more left for the next person who buys a
free Zoni
you mean it's a limited Supply then why
don't they just have an unlimited Supply
if only they could but that would cost
too much money
cost too much money I see I didn't think
of that because I myself have a lot of
money that's okay my lovely lemon
Airhead it's not your fault because you
didn't know it's those gosh darn poor
people how about we go look for
something in the candy aisle instead
candy
[Music]
is that your son Mr Montclair my he's
grown so much he's getting handsome just
like his father
how's everything at home Bartle B is he
sick why is he ignoring us
sorry about that he's getting Shire by
the day maybe it's because I'm not
hitting him hard enough
his muscles are gotten so big ever since
he started going to the YMCA
he can how do you feel it now when I
kick him in the back of the head
truly he is a Moncler indeed okay hey
baby boy don't you wander off now and I
better not catch you with any candy
so many yummy sweets and yet I'm not
allowed to have any well why Papa why
must you keep me on such a short leash
have I not been a good boy oh I not
polish your big attractive butt cheeks
with warm sensual palm oils on a nightly
basis
you just sold an entire orphanage by
buying it and threatening to kill the
orphans if their original seller didn't
buy it back at triple the prize so we're
definitely not short on money so I must
you hold me back
[Music]
can wait today
Republic what you doing
you know my name my mom is the queen of
Mobius which makes me the prince so I
know everybody's name it's part of the
job
so you are thanks for letting me have my
birthday here it is a nice Kingdom
indeed except for the dookie stains on
the Voya floor there
sorry about that my brother manicted
that last Christmas after he ate
effective plums
that's okay but I have no doubt my
father will have me clean it because he
loves to make my life a living hell but
this is your birthday party isn't it why
don't you go ask him if you could have a
break I bet he'll say yes if you ask
uh-huh you're funny fat people are
always so funny it's because they have
to overcompensate emotionally because
physically they have little to offer hey
do you wanna be my [__]
no thanks hey do you want some of my
rainbow cupcake sorry my daddy said I
can only have whole milk so my muscles
can get big do you want to be my [__]
no thanks
Mr Mont can I demand a word
Our Queen Alina is the problem my son
just told me that your kid hit him
because he wouldn't become his sugar
baby fuckboy did he know how nice I
guess that means your baby boy has a fat
ass
fat ass Sonic is three years old he's
not old enough to have a fat ass I
disagree
it's not my fault dad he was tempting me
very hard by shaking it in my face then
he tried to give me a cupcake a cupcake
I thought I made the rules Crystal Clear
Sun if you can follow them without a
reason then I must hurt what you love
[Music]
how big of balls must you have to place
a single hand upon one of my three Royal
hedge hoglets I will have your head torn
from your body and placed in my front
lawn man it roll over to your Dad and
tell him to rip up the check
what
the sales off we are no longer selling a
portion of the Kingdom to the montclairs
half you promise you would sell me half
your kingdom for an 89 000 trillion
dollars we had a deal
the deal has been diminished greatly Mr
Montclair you'll be lucky if you even
get one third of the planet Mobius now
you damn fool do you see what you did of
course not your [__] baby a baby
you're close to the family name
[Music]
I'm so sorry my lovely boyfriend if I
only knew
that's quite all right all that matters
is that I am happy now here with you
[Music]
hey Bartleby is it just me or does that
candy bar look like it has your face on
it does it now oh yes I quite forgot
that I was a spokesperson once for this
candy brand
of these golden nuts only the most
delicable candy are in the world
so cool what made you become a
spokesperson for a candy bar
[Music]
some candy
I'm gonna buy it
huh why did you stop my Beach
I want it truly but it's way too
expensive for little old me
but it's only a couple thousand dollars
see I even knocked it down so more lower
class citizens could buy it for their
kitties heart Levy most people don't
have 27 000 plus tax to spend on a candy
bar
they they don't but why are they stupid
oh look they're playing one of my
commercials now maybe that will convince
you
you have not really lived until you put
my salty nuts in your kids mouths
and I'm not talking about my ball sack
so go out and treat your kids to a honey
place not bar and I promise your kids
will love you almost as much as they
love by nuts in their face
34 year old how did you like the taste
of my looking up well it was a little
bit salty Barbie but it was pretty good
hey kids funny twenty seven thousand
dollars you can also have Bobby's nuts
in your [__] mouth
[Music]
so [__] what say you feel like tossing
away a few thousand bucks
I've got 39 cents
laughs
blue Beach seems like I'm always having
to do everything myself around here
what is taking the cashier so long is he
sucking some guys balls in the public
bath
what must rich man do to obtain some
service in this gas station
what is going on
the employee closed up shop for today
and now we'll opt in
flutton oh heavens what will we do
isn't that Friday
that means the store might not be open
again until Monday however will we last
that long
Bart Levy please tell us tell us you
have a plan like you always do
I wish I could but but it appears we may
be trapped you forever or at least until
the employee returns
or dolly beach it's not that bad
honestly now
you're a part of the world famous Sonic
Underground
in fact need I remind you what the Sonic
Underground turns to When Hope is all
but lost
[Music]
[Applause]
cause we are all in this together
getting stronger every day
[Music]
back it up boys we're going to America
to get some of Bobby's fine nuts Yeehaw
[__]
foreign
[Music]
I will beat you I'll beat you really bad
the hill the store still isn't open yet
what's the old up Tim how come you still
haven't done lost the store yet well
Dallas I don't want to ruin the fun
[Music]
do you think
[Applause]
[Music]
together we can always find a way I
can't believe what we achieved look how
many people showed up a Chinese family
from China and a white archaeologist guy
from Egypt
five whole people it's almost as if we
brought the whole world together through
the power of music
Naturally music is a language we all
speak no matter where we hail from music
in in itself is a special part that we
all share
now give some sugar to your papa
by the way Bartleby you never did finish
your story
didn't I
um where did I leave off again
[Music]
curse to the family now
hey birthday boy you got a minute
you're the king of Mobius Mr Hedgehog I
didn't mean to hurt your son he just
made me mad so I [__] specked him
like the little [__] he was it's all
right son I think he kind of liked it
actually haha hey will you spare a
moment and talk with me there's
something I'd like to discuss with your
ass let's head to the balcony over there
I can see your dad is rough on you I for
one would never treat my own children in
such a way
and perhaps it isn't my place to step in
but I would like to give you some advice
nonetheless
if you'll allow it of course
some advice listen Bartleby in your life
you're going to meet plenty of people
most of which won't be as sexy or sweet
and kind like yourself
take this party for example the guests
are more concerned about your family
inheritance than your birthday party
even your cake is cheaply made
instead of buying it directly from the
Pillsbury Doughboy company your dad
ordered a box mix from Kmart through
door Dash and stayed up late into the
night making it by hand also he wouldn't
have to spend extra money on you by
having the butler do it that is how much
he hates you
that is how jealous he is of you
yet even after I told you all this I
want you to do one simple thing
just smile
smile smile whenever you're around
people Bartleby
smart people laugh it off when
Misfortune finds them kids will like you
adults will too
people will always look towards those
who have a kind heart
that is one thing I learned as king
so go to him find my son smile and make
peace
because he needs someone like you in his
life
hey fellow baby sorry for spanking you
and calling you my [__] well not really
but your dad said I should or he might
not let you come to my birthday parties
anymore so go tell him he made up before
I ripped off your diaper poop in it and
put it back on you as punishment
then then I'll forgive you if you play
with me for the rest of the day and you
have to hold my hand and spank my butt
I was going to do that anyway
[Music]
my father I wish I could remember him
I do too [__]
I do too
[Music]
now tell me what is this roll Taquito
you speak out oh dear it's just tack we
know that cooks while it's being rolled
aquito
[Music]
foreign foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
thank you
foreign
[Music]